<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="hello">Hello World, SplashActivity!</string>
	<string name="app_name">CodeGreen</string>
	<string name="review_dialog_title">Add Review</string>
	<string name="submit_button">Submit</string>
	<string name="cancel_button">Cancel</string>
	<string name="add_review">Add Review</string>
	<string name="review_submitted">Review submitted successfully.</string>
	<string name="record_saved">Article saved successfully.</string>
	<string name="no_reviews">No Reviews submitted yet.</string>
	<string name="submitted_by">Submitted by:</string>
	<string name="submitted_by_anonymous">Submitted by anonymous</string>
	<string name="reviews">Reviews:</string>
	<string name="saved_already">Article already saved</string>
	<string name="str_design_arech">DESIGN &amp; ARCHI</string>
	<string name="str_sci_tech">SCIENCE &amp; TECH</string>
	<string name="str_trans">TRANSPORT &amp; TRAVEL</string>
	<string name="str_food_health">FOOD &amp; HEALTH</string>
	<string name="str_about"> Our quest is to make Green not a niche but the
		mainstream kind and under the umbrella of “Code Green” “Spire world
		aims to sensitise the business world towards the economic,
		environmental and social benefits of adopting Green infrastructure,
		technologies and practices.”
		\n In this modern era every corporate’s agenda quotes ‘Green’. Many
		practices under corporate responsibility are different shades of green
		– from using recycled paper to making buildings that follow eco
		friendly methods. They have set their foundations upon optimal usage
		of resources and replenishing renewable resources – using to its
		maximum, that which is abundant in nature and saving resources which
		are scarce.
		\n Spire World’s philosophy of Mainstream Green strives to successfully
		combine commercial market imperatives and practices with core values
		regarding environmental sustainability. Eventually it appeals to our
		sense of responsibility towards both the natural and urban
		environment.
		\n Under the Mainstream Green philosophy, we aim to raise the awareness and
		form a medium for communication, so that the community is up to speed
		on how green, productivity and bottom lines are closely interlinked.
		The intent is to reach out, to connect existing points of
		entrepreneurship that dot the landscape with ideas and innovation with
		a green thread.</string>
</resources>
